Stand back, stand back from that door.
后退，后退到门那边去
You're right! It is them!
你说对了！就是他们！
Quick! Get out of it!
快！你们快跑！
No!
不！
Remain still.
不要动
You devils! You killed him! An unarmed man!
你们这群魔鬼！你们杀死了他！一个手无寸铁的人！
Get up.
起来
You are known to us.
我们知道你
And you to me.
我也知道你们
Who is in command?
这里谁说了算？
I am.
我
You will be needed.
你是需要的
What have you done with my men?
你把我的人都怎么样了
They will return.
他们会回来
They're not dead?!
他们没死
No. They are not dead. They are altered.
没，他们没死，他们只是被改造了
Altered? What have you done to them?
改造？你们对他们干了什么
They are now controlled.
他们现在是被控制的
If you do anything to my...
如果你敢伤害我的...
You will do nothing.
你什么也做不了
You will now take us to the control centre.
你将带我们去控制中心
I'll be damned...
我真该死...
Through here.
走这边
You will remain here. If you leave
you will be converted like the others.
你们待在这里．如果你们离开, 你们会像其他人一样被转化
Survey party, come in, we are not receiving you, over.
调查小组, 请回话, 我们没有收到你们的信息．结束
Can we see the control antenna from here?
我们从这里可以看到控制天线吗？
No, Roger. It's just around that first block
just outside the main port.
不能, Roger．它正好在主舱门外面第一区域的外面
So, we have to send somebody outside so get ready...
看来, 我们得派个人出去做好准备...
We have to...
我们必须...
Get back! Get back! These things are lethal!
回来！回来！这些东西是致命的fixme
None will move.
谁也不要动
If you move you will be killed.
谁动谁就没命了
What are they?! How did they get in!?
他们是什么？！怎么进来的？
Silence! We are Cybermen!
安静！我们是赛博人！
But you were all killed!
但你们都被干掉了啊！
We are going to take over the Gravitron
我们要接管"引力创"
And use it to destroy the surface of the Earth
by changing the weather.
用它来改变天气, 毁灭地球表面
But that will kill everybody on the Earth.
但那会杀死地球上的所有人
Yes.
是的
You're supposed to be so advanced. Here you are,
taking your revenge like children.
还以为你们是先进文明．现在你们来了，像孩子一样搞复仇
Revenge? What is that?
复仇？那是什么？
A feeling people have...
人类的一种情感...
Feelings? Yes, we know of this weakness of yours.
情感？是的, 我们知道你们的这项弱点
We are fortunate. We do not posses feelings.
我们是幸运的, 我们没有情感
Then why are you here?
那你们干嘛来了?
To eliminate all dangers.
来消除所有危险
But you kill every single thing on the Earth!
但你们要杀死地球上的所有生物！
Yes. All dangers will be eliminated.
是的, 这样所有危险就会消除了
Hey, what do you think you're doing?
嘿, 你觉得你在干什么？
You seem to be better.
你看起来好些了
Aye, I feel myself again.
是, 感觉神志清醒了些
Lie back there!
躺回去！
But I'm better!
但我好多了！
Oh, my head.
噢, 我的头
Well, take it easy, mate.
好了, 放松点, 朋友
At least, you know it is not your McCrimmon piper.
至少, 你知道不是你那个 McCrimmon 风笛手了
It had me worried though, I admit that.
它很让我忧心, 我得承认
Yeah, those Cybermen have got us all worried mate.
是啊, 那些赛博人让我们所有人都忧心
We see them in action before.
我们以前见过他们行动
They must have some weakness.
他们肯定有某种弱点
Well, in my day, they used to sprinkle witches with holy water.
哦, 在我那时候, 他们一般会朝巫婆喷洒圣水
Fat lot of use that would be on them.
那对他们用的可多了(?)
Sprinkle... Holy Water... Ben!
喷洒...圣水... Ben!
What are the Cybermen covered in?
赛博人外面穿的是什么？
As far as I know, their suit is a metal of some sort.
据我所知, 他们的外套是某种金属
What about that thing on their chests? You know the part
that replaced their heart and lungs.
他们胸口那东西呢？你知道他们用那个部件替换了他们的心脏和肺
Some kind of plastic I think.
某种塑料吧, 我想
I thought so. You see, it's simple.
Nail vanish remover dissolves nail vanish.
我觉得是．你看, 很简单, 卸甲油可以溶解指甲油
Nail vanish is a plastic. So we do what Jamie says,
we sprinkle them, see?!
指甲油也是塑料的(?), 所以我们就按 Jamie 所说的, 我们喷他们, 明白了吗？
No, clear as mud if you ask me.
没, 跟泥巴一样, 如果你问我的话
Anyway, I am going to try an experiment.
不管怎样, 我打算进行一项实验
Yes, Professor.
好的, ＂教授＂
Dr. Evans! I thought he was dead.
I thought that they were all dead!
Evans 医生！我以为他已经死了．我以为他们都死了！
Bet if they were by the look of it.
外表看来肯定是啊
Tell the operators in the power unit to come out.
让电力室的操作员出来
Now.
马上
All right, you can all see what is happening.
好吧, 你们都看见了现在的情况
Come on out, leave the machine and don't try anything.
出来吧, 离开机器, 别轻举妄动
They will now take over the Gravitron power unit.
他们现在要接管＂引力创＂的电力室
Yes.
是的
But you can't send them in their without protected helmets.
但你不能让他们不带头盔就进那里去
Why?
为什么
The machine produces very intense sonic fields./
那个机器会产生非常强的声场
Without the helmets, those men will be insane in a few hours!
不带头盔的话, 这些人几个小时就会疯掉的！
How many hours?
几个小时？
Twelve possibly.
大概１２小时
Then there is no problem.
那就没有问题了
Why?
为什么
Our purpose will be achieved before that.
在那之前我们的目的就应该达到了
But what about the men?
但人怎么办？
They will be disposed of.
他们会被丢弃
Now, keep your fingers crossed.
现在, 交叉你的手指祈祷吧
It works!
有效！
But I still don't know what you are on about.
但我还是不懂你在搞什么
If we can sprinkle some of that on their chest units,
it might help to soften them.
如果我们能喷一些这个东西到他们胸口上, 就能软化它
I get it! You mean it will clobber their controls or something.
我明白了！你是说这个能捣烂他们的控制器什么的
Yes, that's it.
对, 就是这样
May the power into the vortex generators now.
将能量注入到涡流发电机上去
What is happening?
怎么回事？
There is loss of control.
这里失去控制了
Now look, we only have one chance at this.
听着, 我们这事只有一次机会
When I open the door, drop down as low as you can,
当我打开门, 尽量俯低身体
aim this things... at their chests and squirt like mad. Right?
将这个东西...对准他们的胸口, 疯了一样猛喷, 明白不?
Right.
明白
Get ready.
预备
Someone is there.
那里有人
Quick, get their chest things!
快, 对准胸口！
Quick, get these things off their heads!
快, 把这些东西从他们脑袋上拿下去
Come on! Quick, there isn't a moment to lose./
快来！快, 我们一秒钟也不能耽搁
We got to get the Gravitron down to safe level.
我们得把＂引力创＂降到安全水平
What about those poor men?
这些可怜的家伙怎么办？
Shift them off to the medical unit, as quick as you can.
搬到医务室去, 迅速
We are not receiving you. We are not receiving you.
我们收不到你的信号, 我们收不到你的信号
They must have failed.
他们肯定已经失败了
Yes. We must invade now. Prepare the weapons.
是的, 我们必须进攻了, 准备好武器
Yes.
是的
Now listen everybody. I don't know how many more
of these Cybermen there are, /
现在, 每个人都听好了．我不知道这些赛博人有多少
but our point of view we are under siege.
I'll reckon they will be back in a bit...
但我们看到的是, 我们已经被包围了．我估计他们很快就会回来...
Now communications. Charlie, keep trying
to get through to Earth. Right?
现在说说通讯. Charlie, 继续尝试联系上地球, 明白不？
Right, will do.
明白, 马上
The rest of you, lower the armoured doors at all exits./
其他人, 关上所有出口的安全门
Make up as much of that gubbins that you got, we may need it.
多造一些你们的那个小装置, 我们可能需要它
Mr Hobson, how far can the probe be lowered down?
Hobson 先生, 那个探测器可以降低到什么程度？
About thirty degrees.
大概３０度
That's no good.
那可不够
What do you mean?
你什么意思？
Can any other part be lowered?
还有其他什么部件可以降低吗？
Well, the main coil lenses can be shifted about
without too much trouble but...
嗯, 主线圈镜头可以移动, 不是太费事, 但是...
There's something outside there!
外面有什么东西！
What is it?
是什么？
It's a long way off.
挺远的地方
I'll come.
我就来